192 COLONIAL DRIVE AKRON. PA 17501

(717)572-1802

DANNYISYELLING@GMAIL.COM

https://dannyliehr.github.io/index.html

DANNY LIEHR

SKILLS

3 years of Graphic Design education and experience. Leadership job in retail. Diplomatic. Creative. 5+ years Photoshop. 5+ years InDesign. Writing in JS for 2 to 3 years. Writing in PHP and Python for 1 year. Writing in HTML and CSS off and on for the past 6 or so years.

EXPERIENCE

PROGRAMMING- "CD" - Solo Project

APR 2018 - ONGOING- Node JS, Server Management

- Learned NodeJS.
- Learned how to use a remote computer and about SSH.
- Learned about cron scheduling.

DUNKIN' DONUTS - Shift Leader

FEB 2018 - AUG 2018

- Learned how to do inventory and designating tasks to employees in a team.
- Assisted Manager in truck orders, and maintained databases.
- Counted and handled money for the manager.
- Reason for leaving: Wrongfully terminated.

A.C. MOORE - Associate

JUN 2019 - AUG 2019

- Customer Service experience.
- Reason for leaving: Scheduling conflict with college.

THADDEUS STEVENS COLLEGE OF TECHNOLOGY - Librarian

FEB 2018 - Current

- Learned the Dewey decimal system.
- Provided tech support for other students.
- Reason for Leaving: Every student is let go at the end of the school year.
 Continually returned.

EDUCATION

Lancaster County Career and Tech Center, Brownstown — Commercial Art

AUG 2012. GRADUATED MAY 2014 (Advanced Placement) GPA: 4.0

Learned various Adobe products and traditional art. Dabbled in Website design. Excelled in Digital Illustration.

Thaddeus Stevens College of Technology, Lancaster — Associate Degree in Applied Science, Computer Software Engineering

JAN 2018 - CURRENT - SOPHOMORE

Applied 2018. Studying software engineering. Made Dean's List first semester. Specialisation: Javascript, PHP, Python.

AWARDS

Lancaster County Youth Artists Silver Medal, 2010. Ephrata Achievement Medallion, 2009. Certificate of Advanced Placement National Occupational Competency Test, 2014.

REFERENCES (NAME, RELATIONSHIP, OCCUPATION)

BRADLEY ADAMS- Former Instructor, Graphics Instructor.

- Phone: (717) 299-7768
- Email: adams@stevenscollege.edu

ADAM MARNOCH- Former Co-worker, Supervisor.

• Phone: (717) 715-4296

ZACH FEDOR Former Instructor, Software Engineering Instructor.

- Phone: (717) 391-7203
- Email: fedor@stevenscollege.edu